(Bernadette:)Come on, Howard,
I'm not falling for that again.
(Howard:)No, here.
(Bernadette:)Oh, Howie, a little star.
(Bernadette:)It's beautiful.
(Bernadette:)Put it on me.
Okay, but I'm gonna have
to get it back from you...
(Howard:)...so I can take it
to the lnternational Space Station.
(Howard:)That way, when I come home...
(Howard:)...you will have a star
that was actually in space.
(Bernadette:)Oh, my God.
(Howard:)Take that, every guy
who's ever bought you anything.
(Bernadette:)This is the most amazing gift
l've ever gotten.
I'm going to the
supermarket to buy snacks for your trip!
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Do you want me to get those
little boxes of Froot Loops you like?